Ugh… this damn bat… it hurts like hell!
…At least this beating wasn't for nothing
Hehe… were you so angry you didn't notice you lost your panties?
Hmph… this cloying, bloody stench
And that faint red mark on your neck…
No doubt about it
It's a mark left by 'Camilla's' crew
How truly filthy
Hmph, I won't let you escape
Sniff sniff… smells good…
Who's there?!
Hmph, so you were hiding here, savoring your master's filth?
What a disgusting habit
Just as expected from a servant of that vampire trash
About that…
…'interesting' bite mark on your neck
I have some questions for you
Answer them honestly
Got it, Mr. Pervert?
To think you'd even dare to steal my panties…
This punishment should teach him a lesson
Wha-what's going on!?
…Did Camilla accidentally save me?
But why is this girl attacking me for no reason…
Damn it, if you're not going to be reasonable, then you can't blame me for what happens next!
You despicable pervert!
Hurry up and… let me go!
Hey, you're the one who attacked me, right?
S-stop!
You filthy thing—!
D-don't touch there… Nngh… Q-quickly, stop—!
Alright, time to dig in!
A-are you kidding me?!
Something this big………!
Come on, relax a little
N-no, that's impossible, right?!
I'll… I'll definitely break!
No, don't!
Agh!—?! It hurts!
You bastard, how d-dare you just shove it in so suddenly—Ugh!
Huh? This feeling, could it be…
Hahaha… I can't believe you're still a virgin!
Nngh—! You damn bastard—!
Pull it out right now! Do you hear me?! …Get… get that thing out of me… P-pull it out—!
How could I let you go so easily?
Aah! It… hurts!
It's okay, a girl like you will get used to it soon enough
Ooh… so soft and tight, with this exquisite texture…!
A fox-girl's virgin pussy, it's really something else…!
You… despicable scum…!
You better remember this…!
This humiliation, I, Hikawa Yuki…
…will never, ever forget!
The day I break free
I'll tear you limb from limb—!!
Oh my, how scary!
But you can only talk tough for now
Shut up! Stop spouting nonsense, you filthy thing!
What, you want me to shut up?
Eek!—
Heehee, stopped squealing?
That's right, girls should be nice and quiet
Your breasts are so big and soft…
Even better than Camilla's
It's getting tighter and tighter inside
Looks like you're feeling it too
How is that possible?!
Being f-forced by something filthy like you—!
How… how could I possibly feel good?!
D-don't be so full of yourself!
You filthy, perverted scum!
Hehehe, I get it, I get it
Your body is much more honest than your mouth
Hah… I'm… I'm about to reach my limit…
Wh-what?! ❤ N-no! W-wait, you filthy thing!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Aaaaaahhh!!! ♥
N-no way…? ❤
I-inside… Nngh…♥…
By the way, tell me your name
We'll have plenty of chances to see each other again